The 1st Ochiaiyo!
Ochiaiyo!
Hello everyone! We
We are Natoya Karumi!
We have a big plan for the performance.
This time
We would like to decide who is the most knowledgeable member
We would like to decide who will be the most knowledgeable members of KIRARI.
Let's take a look at the results of the big project so far.
King Honda is Miyako
And King Nagata is Honda
Oh!
Just do the big one, please.
And King Suganami and King Suzuki are Ogi-chan
That's so strong.
And King Kawaguchi is Momo-kun Sakurai, right?
And King Tomita is Saya Kaninacki.
Full name.
And King Tanizaki is Shomi Tanaka.
Oh!
You guys are amazing!
Is that a nugget?
I still don't have a shot at the king.
I'm not aiming for the king.
Somebody's got a nugget.
Yay!
The king's name is waiting for us.
We've got to go for it.
Someone with confidence
That's what it looks like
I'm not confident.
I'm not.
This is really
It's true.
But... we're together a lot, aren't we?
We've been together since the auditions.
That's right.
But I want you to listen to me for a second.
Why?
I was King Tomita the other day.
What about you, Kirari?
What?
Oh, I can't do it anymore.
Let's go for it.
Yes!
We're the same.
Then have her be Kirari.
Let's go for it.
Let's do our best.
Let's do our best, as if we were Kirari.
Let's get on with it.
Okay.
Here's the first question.
How tall are you?
What?
To the nearest hundredth.
Yes, sir.
What?
To a decimal point.
Is this easy?
Easy?
What?
Has it grown recently?
No? - I don't know.
I don't know.
What?
I haven't grown since four years ago.
Oh, really?
I don't know that either.
You know what I mean.
I knew it.
Yeah.
It's supposed to be on the official website.
Yabba-babba.
I could have written that.
I could write it.
Now that we've all written it, let's open it up.
Let's open it up!
Open!
That's it!
What's that?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Big, big, big.
I can't write this.
Correct.
49.54.
48.6
My dream 150
I'm going to be in the kitchen.
My finger stopped.
Thank you.
Answers, please.
140.
18.5.
Oh, that's close!
So close!
It's so close!
It's too close!
You're right, Nacchan, it's too close.
How about this decimal point?
What if there's 5 points?
What if there's a 5?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's close! So close!
Nacchan, 0.5!
0.2!
Yes!
It's important that the decimal point plays a big role.
I'm going to eat more of these points...
Now the second question, please.
How many 3's have you eaten so far?
How many 3's?
Are you counting? Are you counting?
I've eaten a lot since I was a little girl.
What? Are you counting?
Bye-bye.
You're lying!
It's not like it's a specific number.
One, two, three.
Ready?
Let's do it!
Ten thousand, five thousand.
Three thousand two hundred and fifty.
30,000?
How did you do the math?
At one a day, that's 10 years.
How old am I now?
That's right.
I miscalculated.
You miscalculated.
It could be more.
Let's see how many you've eaten.
Go ahead!
Please!
Let's see...
Kirari Ochiai's Mens Mood
That's right.
I see.
I told you so.
Bread and soba noodles are ready.
I can't have tea.
It's made of bread from toe to toe.
Something interesting and bread-colored.
It doesn't look delicious.
It looks like it's made of bread.
Looks delicious.
Thank you very much.
I don't have to think too hard.
I don't have to think hard.
I got it now.
Third question, please.
If you were a character, how would you describe yourself?
Character?
A character that exists like this?
You're asking for a lot of clues, aren't you?
I don't get it.
You're scaring me, even though you're telling me the right answer.
It's a character.
Are you giving me an answer that I don't understand, too?
No, I think this is relatively normal.
Then what is normal?
Do you guys know?
But which is it?
I know the right answer.
Next.
Killacuma.
Hey, baby.
I have a lot of questions.
First.
Which one's the baby?
The one who makes Ammerman bread.
The one who makes it.
This one.
The one who makes the bread.
Kilakter.
Ammerman.
What are you following up on?
You say you want me to be a hero and protect you.
Ammerman.
By the way, what was the other thing you were wondering?
What do you mean, you were wondering about something else?
What was the other thing you were wondering?
Killakter.
Kirakutor.
But I think I might have figured it out.
Kilakter.
It's hard.
Killakter.
Killakter?
Killaktar.
Killacter.
Kiraktar.
I'm lost too, Killakter.
I'm made of my face, too.
I was lost too, Kiraktar.
I'm lost too, Kiraktar.
I'm made of my own face.
I've done it myself.
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy.
You were so sure of yourself.
I don't look like me.
They say I don't look like me.
Zero.
Oh, really?
That's good.
There's a reason I had it done.
It's gonna be a couple of hours.
That's so frustrating.
It is frustrating.
He's so cute.
Let's go next time.
Next question, please.
How would you react if someone said, "Your outfit today is sparkly.
Put it back on Kiralee.
Try being Kiralee.
Oh, thank you.
You say it.
I'll tell you.
Okay, I'll go.
Yes, it's just that I've got the blinkers on today.
I'll go.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm a glittering mess.
Pan pansy.
Come on, come on, come on.
I'm really simple.
Really simple.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy, happy, happy.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's pretty.
But is there glitter on it?
It's the same with the outfit.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I'm starting to be aware of it.
I'm feeling self-conscious.
From the costume.
I'm trying to be upbeat.
It's getting closer.
But I'm saying I'm becoming more aware of my chi.
I'm chi-conscious, even though it's got Mars in it.
Hey, Mars, no, no, no, no.
He's so far away.
Yay.
Let's go, let's go.
Yay!
.5
I want to take a cool shot next time!
Fifth question, please.
Kirari Ochiai up to her signature pose
321.
What pose did you take?
Wasn't that easy?
Oh, wow.
That's great.
All three of us.
Three twenty-one.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my gosh, are we all together?
Everybody together?
Oh!
Flatland.
Okay.
What if it's not this one?
This is all I can think of, right?
Right, of course.
I'll listen to the answer as it is.
Oh!
Wait a minute.
Am I too much like you?
You're right.
Maybe we're too much alike.
Three twenty-one.
Uh-oh.
0.5.
That's great!
Congratulations.
121.
Thank you.
That's a relief.
Next time...
Let's do it!
That means there are only 3 questions left.
Okay.
Two points for Suzuki.
Seven points.
Ran has 2 points
I have 1 point
Well, well, well.
Good consultation.
I think we still have a chance to make up for it.
Really?
I think we can do it.
All right.
Next topic.
What was your first impression of Nanaka Tomita?
She's asking the same questions I am.
That's right.
I'm in trouble.
I wonder how much confidence Nanaka has in me.
I wonder...
It's just a hunch.
Open for two, please!
Ready?
That's it!
Hey!
You're pretending to be Mr. Tomita. - No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Two points for you.
Two points
Two points.
Two.
Two points
2 points
3 points
4 points
5 points
6 points
7 points
8 points
9 points
10 points
11 points
12 points
13 points
14 points
15 points
16 points
17 points
18 points
19 points
20 points
23 points
24 points
25 points
26 points
27 points
28 points
29 points
30 points
31 points
34 points
35 points
36 points
37 points
38 points
39 points
40 points
41 points
42 points
43 points
44 points
45 points
46 points
47 points
48 points
50 points
51 points
52 points
53 points
54 points
55 points
56 points
57 points
58 points
59 points
60 points
61 points
62 points
63 points
64 points
65 points
67 points
68 points
79 points
70 points
71 points
72 points
73 points
74 points
75 points
66 points
67 points
78 points
98 points
99 points
90 points
91 points
92 points
93 points
84 points
95 points
96 points
97 points
98 points
99 points
10 points
11 points
12 points
13 points
14 points
15 points
16 points
There's some kind of word in there.
Here we go.
Happy here, happy there, happy there, happy here, happy there, happy there, happy there, happy there, happy there, happy there, happy there, happy there, happy there, happy there.
He was in a jikawaguchi gachi
Yay
You're good at making them!
If you write so many happy things, it's like...
LOL
Quite a lot of entertainment.
You're right.
That's really nice.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Normally, I'm happy.
Tickets, Captain. Backstage at the concert.
Happy!
Happy, happy, happy.
As you can see every day
Everyone is really good!
Really?
So good.
I wonder what Hinari came up with.
That's what she's going to see.
I wonder...
I wonder if she's asleep.
Is she awake?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Our captain, Captain Happy.
I want to deliver it.
I want to find it, I want to find it, GO!
Captain Natsume's Boonz
Oh!
That's so cool!
Awesome!
Ah!
If you put it in words
Let me put it in words.
First of all...
Do you want to do it on the tappie?
I'll do the tappie!
I'll do the first one.
Okay, one point at a time.
Yes!
First one.
One point each.
Yeah!
Two points.
People with Natsume in
Nah, the one with Nacchan in it.
Not quite.
Aah!
Who has Natsume in it?
Ah!
Who's in Kamaguchi?
Yes.
You're in.
One point!
A point!
Points for everyone. - Minus one.
Minus one for everyone.
Yay!
But your rap is so good.
I kinda want you to make one of your own.
What?
You're right, I did.
I made you one.
And now, on to the next one.
Yo!
YO!
Yes!
Oh, please!
Wow!
Be Hitomi Suzuki.
Please do a self-promotion
Please do it!
I don't know.
There are so many places to do self-promotion.
There are so many places to do it.
That's true.
Being in idol group...
I'm probably the second worst at it.
Self-promotion.
Second worst.
I'm a mono-boke.
Oh, I see.
I'll give you the last clue.
PR... is...
Self-introduction.
It might be easier to answer if you think of it as self-introduction.
It might be easier to answer.
Right. Um...
Oh, I see.
What do you mean?
What do you do that you don't like?
That's a hint.
Oh, that's a hint?
Seriously, it's time to start exaggerating.
Yes, sir.
Oh, you got it?
Yes, I did.
Okay, I'll start with my answer.
How about a Coke with a note to Hitomi Suzuki?
Rin is delicious.
Everyone's going to go for Suzuki's red.
Wait a minute.
You're right.
What's wrong with that?
What is it?
Shall we write it down?
Yes.
Hitomi's Hitomi with a note.
I'm Hitomi Suzuki, aka Suzuki Chan.
Konitaire Kyun.
Wow, that's great.
Here we go.
I always deliver with my forehead.
It's Suzuki's Suzuki.
My bangs are udochi.
The most intense rain of heat for you.
Connie Tail Kyun is here today, too.
Thanks for everything, Connie.
Uh-uh.
I'm not sure.
Wait a minute.
I'm fronting.
Why are you doing this Tufkin thing?
It's the second half of the scene.
From then on, I thought he was innocent.
There's something in there about doing it.
I'm gonna be pissed.
I'm gonna be pissed, but I'm gonna do it.
Oh!
Hi-chan, I've been crushed by everyone's love.
I'll get mad if you cheat on me again.
I love her.
I thought she'd wait for me...
Let's crush her...
Oh, no!
It's not even close.
Not even close.
A mushroom came out of the tree!
What's with the mushrooms?
It's not the same at all!
I'm not involved in anything
Are you close with Nasaka?
I guess so.
Not even close.
What on earth?
Would you like to hear the result?
Yes, sir.
Suzuki scored 4.7
Nacchan scored 4
I scored 4.
Oh!
That's what it means.
The Rakiai King is
Suzuki alone
The winner is Suzuki!
Congratulations!
I'm so happy.
I won by two today.
Well, maybe by 0.7 points, but...
But 4.7 points is important.
Yes, it is.
It's important.
Okay, that's all for now.
That's all for now.
Meow!
Bye, bye, bye.